Nevada Folklife Archive
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Photographs
  - Subseries 1: Slides, 8,390 still images (.jpg); 8,390 still images (.tif); 14,257 still images (.jpg); 14,257 still images (.tif)
    - Grave markers Lincoln County, June 6, 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-126 - S-1987-128; Michael Luster; 52 color slides (35mm) (Box 28)
    - Pierson Ranch, May 17, 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-129; Michael Luster; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 28)
    - Basque aspen carvings and sheep herders cabin, May 18, 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-130; Michael Luster; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 28)
    - Sampete County, Utah, May 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-131; Blanton Owen; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 28)
    - 18 Mile Ranch, May 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-132 - S-1987-133; Blanton Owen; 30 color slides (35mm) (Box 28)
    - Jordan Valley, Oregon, May 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-134; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 28)
    - [Jordan Valley, Oregon; Caliente; Delmue Ranch], May 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-135; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 28)
    - [Architecture], May 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-136 - S-1987-137; Blanton Owen; 35 color slides (35mm) (Box 29)
    - Delmue Ranch, June 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-138; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 29)
    - Fiddler's contest, June 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-139; Blanton Owen; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 29)
    - Delmue Ranch, June 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-140 - S-1987-143; Blanton Owen; 77 color slides (35mm) (Box 29)
    - Frank Ernst and Dutch ovens, June 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-144; Andrea Graham; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 29)
    - [Architecture], June 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-145 - S-1987-146; Blanton Owen; 33 color slides (35mm) (Box 29)
    - Fiddler's convention, June 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-147; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 29)
    - Austin Fiddler's contest, June 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-148; Blanton Owen; 12 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - Bob Steward Ranch, May 29, 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-149; Michael Luster; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - [Conaway Ranch], May 21, 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-150; Michael Luster; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - [Dutch ovens; Latter Day Saints], June 10, 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-151; Michael Luster; 12 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - Bristol Wells coke ovens, cabins, June 16, 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-152; Michael Luster; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - [Post Office], June 20, 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-153; Michael Luster; 9 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - [Panaca], June 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-154; Michael Luster; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - [Kim Jensen], May 13, 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-155; Michael Luster; 12 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - [Mervin Baker], May 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-156; Michael Luster; 13 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - [Panaca], May 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-157; Michael Luster; 9 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - [Caliente], May 22, 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-158; Michael Luster; 10 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - [Virginia City], 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-159; Andrea Graham; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - Gravestones, August 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-160; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - [Belmont], September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-161; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - [Stone House Ranch], September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-162 - S-1987-163; Blanton Owen; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 30)
    - [Pine Creek and Mosquito Creek Ranches], September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-164; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 31)
    - [Mosquito Creek Ranch], September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-165 - S-1987-166; Blanton Owen; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 31)
    - Mud buildings on Monitor Valley Ranch, September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-167 - S-1987-169; Blanton Owen; 60 color slides (35mm) (Box 31)
    - Mud buildings on Monitor Valley Ranch (1-2); Mud buildings on Visbeck Ranch (3-20), September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-170; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 31)
    - Mud buildings on Visbeck Ranch, September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-171; Blanton Owen; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 31)
    - Log architecture, September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-172; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 31)
    - Vernacular architecture, September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-173 - S-1987-174; Blanton Owen; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 31)
    - Vernacular architecture, September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-175 - S-1987-176; Blanton Owen; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 32)
    - Labor Day in Pioche, September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-177 - S-1987-181; Blanton Owen; 90 color slides (35mm) (Box 32)
    - Vernacular architecture, September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-182; Blanton Owen; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 32)
    - [Yerington graveyard], September 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-183 - S-1987-184; Blanton Owen; 30 color slides (35mm) (Box 32)
    - [Exhibit; Vernacular architecture], December 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-185; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 32)
    - [Likely 18 Mile Ranch], December 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-186 - S-1987-187; 28 color slides (35mm) (Box 32)
    - [Mud houses; Latter Day Saints celebration], July 1987, AFC 2017/002: S-1987-188; Blanton Owen; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 33)
    - [Thunder Mountain folk art environment], January 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-001 - S-1988-002; Blanton Owen; 33 color slides (35mm) (Box 33)
    - [Ackerman Ranch], March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-003 - S-1988-008; Andrea Graham; 116 color slides (35mm) (Box 33)
    - Making horsehair mecarte, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-009 - S-1988-011; Andrea Graham; 60 color slides (35mm) (Box 33)
    - Hair rope making, ranch architecture and equipment, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-012; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 34)
    - Cowboy gear, food, ranch architecture, working cows, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-013; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 34)
    - Working cows, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-014; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 34)
    - Ranching, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-015; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 34)
    - Ranch architecture, working cattle, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-016; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 34)
    - Working cows, architecture, food, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-017; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 34)
    - Ranch architecture, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-018 - S-1988-019; Andrea Graham; 38 color slides (35mm) (Box 34)
    - Ranching, crafts, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-020; Andrea Graham; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 34)
    - Ranching, mining town, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-021; Andrea Graham; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 34)
    - Ranch architecture, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-022; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 34)
    - Domestic architecture, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-023; Andrea Graham; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 35)
    - Mining, architecture, cemeteries, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-024; Andrea Graham; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 35)
    - [Silver Creek Ranch], March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-025 - S-1988-026; Andrea Graham; 36 color slides (35mm) (Box 35)
    - [Austin], March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-027; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 35)
    - Austin Cemetery, April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-028 - S-1988-030; Andrea Graham; 34 color slides (35mm) (Box 35)
    - [Reese River Valley Ranch], April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-031; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 35)
    - [Smith Creek Ranch], April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-032; Andrea Graham; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 35)
    - [Austin], March 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-033 - S-1988-035; Andrea Graham; 55 color slides (35mm) (Box 36)
    - Aerial views of ranches, April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-036; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 36)
    - [Battle Mountain], April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-037 - S-1988-038; Andrea Graham; 38 color slides (35mm) (Box 36)
    - [Lander], April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-039; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 36)
    - Home Ranch, April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-040 - S-1988-042; Andrea Graham; 53 color slides (35mm) (Box 36)
    - [Battle Mountain], April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-043; Andrea Graham; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 36)
    - Tour of underground Kingston Mine with mine safety director Darrel King, May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-044 - S-1988-047; Andrea Graham; 80 color slides (35mm) (Box 36)
    - Tour of underground Kingston Mine with mine safety director Darrel King, May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-048 - S-1988-050; Andrea Graham; 60 color slides (35mm) (Box 37)
    - [Ranch buildings], May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-051 - S-1988-052; Andrea Graham; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 37)
    - Tour of Copper Canyon Mine, Battle Mountain Gold, with safety director Lou Chambliss, May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-053 - S-1988-056; Andrea Graham; 79 color slides (35mm) (Box 37)
    - [Ranch buildings], May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-057; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 37)
    - [Craft work of Gladys Williams and Saggie Williams], May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-058; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 37)
    - Battle Mountain (1-10); Austin (12-15); Dunphy (16-20), May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-059; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 38)
    - [Dunphy Ranch], May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-060; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 38)
    - [Racetrack Ranch], May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-061; Andrea Graham; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 38)
    - [Iowa Canyon Ranch], May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-062 - S-1988-063; Andrea Graham; 37 color slides (35mm) (Box 38)
    - [Vaughn Ranch], May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-064; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 38)
    - [Ranch buildings], May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-065; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 38)
    - Austin (19-20), May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-066; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 38)
    - [Bernice Hooper craft work], May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-067; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 38)
    - Aerials of ranch layouts, corrals, June 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-068; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 38)
    - Gridley Days celebration, June 18, 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-069; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 38)
    - Gridley Days celebration, June 18, 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-070; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 39)
    - [Railroad tie buildings], August 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-071; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 39)
    - Nixon All Indian rodeo, August 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-072; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 39)
    - FAA 1989 Randy Stowell (master) and George Nix (apprentice), rawhide braiding apprenticeship at Randy's ranch, December 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-073 - S-1988-075; Blanton Owen; 58 color slides (35mm) (Box 39)
    - FAA 1989 [Agnes Foster and Harriet Allen], December 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-078 - S-1988-082; Blanton Owen; 108 color slides (35mm) (Box 39)
    - [Lander County], May 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-083; Andrea Graham; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 40)
    - Crittendon ranch buildings, April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-084; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 40)
    - [LS Ranches], April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-085 - S-1988-086; Blanton Owen; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 40)
    - [LS Ranches; Montello Ranch], April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-087; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 40)
    - [Tom Carter], April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-088; Blanton Owen; 6 color slides (35mm) (Box 40)
    - [Thunder Mountain sculptures], April 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-089; Blanton Owen; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 40)
    - [Smith Valley Cemetery], September 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-090; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 40)
    - [Gravestones at Minden], September 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-091; Andrea Graham; 4 color slides (35mm) (Box 40)
    - [Aerials of Lander County; Crittendon Ranch], September 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-092; Andrea Graham; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 40)
    - [Reno Air Races], September 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-093 - S-1988-094; Blanton Owen; 28 color slides (35mm) (Box 40)
    - [Nixon Indian Rodeo], September 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-095; Blanton Owen; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 40)
    - Nevada State Heritage Quilt Project, September 1988, AFC 2017/002: S-1988-096; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 40)
    - FAA 1989, January 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-001 - S-1989-003; Blanton Owen; 47 color slides (35mm) (Box 41)
    - [Sheep camps], March 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-004 - S-1989-011; Blanton Owen; 149 color slides (35mm) (Box 41)
    - Aerials of San Xavier Mission (1-8); Mexican graveyard (9-20), May 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-012; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 42)
    - [Mexican Cemetery], May 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-013; Blanton Owen; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 42)
    - Church, near Tucson in Sonora, Mexico (1-4); Paris, Idaho (5-12); Tuffy the wonder dog, graveyard (13-20), May 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-014; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 42)
    - [Paris, Idaho], June 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-015; Blanton Owen; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 42)
    - Dressler Ranch (1-13); Beatty mine (14-20), July 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-016; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 42)
    - [Reno], July 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-017; Blanton Owen; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 42)
    - [Beatty, Church in Las Vegas], July 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-018; Blanton Owen; 5 color slides (35mm) (Box 42)
    - [Las Vegas], July 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-019 - S-1989-020; Blanton Owen; 32 color slides (35mm) (Box 42)
    - Street Rod Shop (1-15), July 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-021; Blanton Owen; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 42)
    - [Reno], July 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-022; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 42)
    - [Beatty], July 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-023; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 43)
    - [Las Vegas; Sheep camps], July 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-024; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 43)
    - [Architecture], July 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-025; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 43)
    - [Delmue Camp], July 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-026; Blanton Owen; 13 color slides (35mm) (Box 43)
    - [Sheep camps; Aerials], September 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-027; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 43)
    - [Aerials; Basque monument], September 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-028; Blanton Owen; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 43)
    - [Portraits; Crowds at festival], September 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-029; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 43)
    - [Architecture], September 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-030; Blanton Owen; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 43)
    - FAA 1990 Spider Teller's saddle shop, September 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-031; Blanton Owen; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 43)
    - FAA 1990, October 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-032; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 43)
    - [Aerials], 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-033; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 44)
    - FAA 1990, September 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-034 - S-1989-037; Blanton Owen; 57 color slides (35mm) (Box 44)
    - [Pilgrim Rest Baptist Church; Uncle Ben's Barbecue], December 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-038; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 44)
    - [Aerials of Dry Creek Ranch], December 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-039; Blanton Owen; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 44)
    - [Sheep camps], September 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1989-040; Blanton Owen; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 44)
    - [Branding near Elko], April 1990, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-001 - S-1990-002; Blanton Owen; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 44)
    - [Branding near Elko], April 1990, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-003 - S-1990-006; Blanton Owen; 65 color slides (35mm) (Box 45)
    - Copy photos of originals by Arthur Biale, Eureka, Nevada; Photos copied during research on Italian charcoal burners for (ARS) Archaeological Research Services, undated, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-007; Arthur Biale; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 45)
    - [Restaurants in Las Vegas], 1990, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-008; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 45)
    - FAA 1991 photos: Petan IYP Ranch (1-10); Quarter Circle S Ranch (11-17), August 1990, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-009; Andrea Graham; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 45)
    - FAA 1991, August 1990, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-010; Andrea Graham; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 45)
    - FAA 1991, Saddle shop, September 1990, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-011 - S-1990-012; Andrea Graham; 31 color slides (35mm) (Box 45)
    - Dressler Ranch, Douglas County, south of Minden, April 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-013 - S-1990-014; Andrea Graham; 39 color slides (35mm) (Box 45)
    - [Carson Valley], April 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-015 - S-1990-017; Andrea Graham; 54 color slides (35mm) (Box 46)
    - [Genoa Cemetery], July 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-018; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 46)
    - [Genoa Cemetery; Minden Welding Shop], July 1989, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-019; Andrea Graham; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 46)
    - [Quilting], September 1990, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-020; Andrea Graham; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 46)
    - Tucson Meet Yourself, October 1990, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-021 - S-1990-022; Andrea Graham; 25 color slides (35mm) (Box 46)
    - Wa-Pai-Shone Culture Day, Menely Elementary School, Gardnerville, October 27, 1990, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-023 - S-1990-026; Andrea Graham; 79 color slides (35mm) (Box 46)
    - FAA 1991, September 1990, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-027 - S-1990-031; Andrea Graham; 86 color slides (35mm) (Box 47)
    - Serving and eating at annual Washoe Cultural Dinner, held at Washoe Senior Center, December 15, 1990, AFC 2017/002: S-1990-032 - S-1990-033; Andrea Graham; 33 color slides (35mm) (Box 47)
    - FAA 1991 Apprenticeship in Washoe round baskets, January 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-001 - S-1991-002; Andrea Graham; 35 color slides (35mm) (Box 47)
    - FAA 1990, January 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-003; Andrea Graham; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 47)
    - FAA 1990 apprenticeship in saddlemaking Alan McDonald (apprentice), January 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-004; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 47)
    - FAA 1990 apprenticeship in saddlemaking Alan McDonald (apprentice), January 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-005; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 48)
    - IL Ranch, January 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-006; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 48)
    - [Petan Ranch], January 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-007; Andrea Graham; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 48)
    - FAA 1991 apprenticeship in rawhide braiding J.P. Pedrini (apprentice), Randy Stowell (master), January 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-008 - S-1991-010; Andrea Graham; 60 color slides (35mm) (Box 48)
    - Jose Gutierrez performance at Nevada State Museum and High School, March 30, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-011; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 48)
    - Hula class taught by Wayne Panoke at Fern Adair Studio, April 10, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-012; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 48)
    - Hula class taught by Wayne Panoke at Fern Adair Studio (1-7); Polish papercuts (8-14), April 10, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-013; Andrea Graham; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 48)
    - [Basque Music Festival], April 20, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-014; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 49)
    - National Heritage Fellows performances at Nevada State Museum and High School, May 4, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-015 - S-1991-016; Andrea Graham; 39 color slides (35mm) (Box 49)
    - [Alyssa and Stacy Gibbs buckskin tanning], 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-017; Andrea Graham; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 49)
    - Branding at Geyser Ranch, leased by Randy Stowell, May 12, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-018 - S-1991-020; Andrea Graham; 57 color slides (35mm) (Box 49)
    - Slide duplicates from American Folklife Center, Library of Congress, Italian Americans in the West series, October 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-021; Andrea Graham; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 49)
    - [Geyser Ranch], May 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-029; Andrea Graham; 10 color slides (35mm) (Box 49)
    - [Performances at Nevada State Museum], May 25, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-030; Andrea Graham; 12 color slides (35mm) (Box 49)
    - Living Traditions Festival (LTF), Salt Lake City, Utah, May 18, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-031; Andrea Graham; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 49)
    - Living Traditions Festival (LTF), Salt Lake City, Utah, May 18, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-032 - S-1991-033; Andrea Graham; 26 color slides (35mm) (Box 50)
    - Mexican Rodeo, Yerington Fair Grounds, July 6, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-034 - S-1991-035; Andrea Graham; 39 color slides (35mm) (Box 50)
    - Ione Days Drilling Contest, September 1, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-036; Andrea Graham; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 50)
    - Las Vegas Survey, Woodlawn Cemetery, Las Vegas, September 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-037 - S-1991-038; Andrea Graham; 32 color slides (35mm) (Box 50)
    - Las Vegas Survey, Hawaiian festival, Lorenzi Park, Las Vegas, September 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-039 - S-1991-041; Andrea Graham; 51 color slides (35mm) (Box 50)
    - Reno Hispanic Festival, September 15, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-042 - S-1991-043; Andrea Graham; 26 color slides (35mm) (Box 50)
    - FAA 1991-1992, Basque dance apprenticeship, September 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-044; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 50)
    - FAA 1991-1992, Basque dance apprenticeship, University of Nevada, Reno Basque Dancers at Hispanic Heritage Festival, September 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-045 - S-1991-046; Andrea Graham; 38 color slides (35mm) (Box 51)
    - FAA 1991-1992, September 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-047 - S-1991-050; Andrea Graham; 78 color slides (35mm) (Box 51)
    - FAA 1991-1992 Angie McGarva and Tamea Knight, Shoshone beadwork, at Angie's house in Lee, November 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-051; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 51)
    - FAA 1991-1992 Shoshone beadwork, November 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-052; Andrea Graham; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 51)
    - FAA 1991-1992 apprenticeship in Shoshone basketry, Emma Bobb (master), Brenda Hooper and Jeanette Losh (apprentices), November 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-053; Andrea Graham; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 51)
    - FAA 1991-1992 Washoe basketry, JoAnn Martinez and Cynthia Foster, November 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-054 - S-1991-056; Andrea Graham; 60 color slides (35mm) (Box 51)
    - Cowboy exhibit and demonstrations, Lied Discovery Children's Museum, December 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-057; Andrea Graham; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)
    - [Quilting], December 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-058; Andrea Graham; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)
    - [Navajo rug weaving], October 27, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-100; Lesley Williams; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)
    - Photos taken at home of Dennis and Norma Naranjo, Las Vegas, November 9, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-101; Lesley Williams; 12 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)
    - Photos taken at McCabe home, Las Vegas, Herbert McCabe's silverwork, stoneleaf and Mitzi McCabe's beadwork, November 9, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-102; Lesley Williams; 8 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)
    - Photos taken at Katherine Duncan's home, Las Vegas. Simba African Dance Troupe performing at African American Cultural Society meeting, November 10, 1991, AFC 2017/002: S-1991-103 - S-1991-105; Lesley Williams; 47 color slides (35mm) (Box 52)